{
  "minecraft-version": "إصدار ماينكرافت",
  "plugin-load-problem": "لا يمكن تحميل الاضافة ال '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "pocketmine-version": "Pocketmine version",
  "bedrock-version": "Bedrock version",
  "forge-version": "اصدار فورج (للتعديلات)",
  "magma-version": "Magma version",
  "authme-shutdown-problem": "The plugin 'AuthMe' fails to load and shuts the server down.",
  "pex-config-problem": "The configuration of the plugin 'PermissionsEx' is invalid.",
  "ambiguous-plugin-name-problem": "There are multiple plugin files for the plugin name '{{plugin-name}}': '{{first-plugin-path}}' and '{{second-plugin-path}}'.",
  "plugin-dependency-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' is missing the required the plugin '{{dependency-plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-disabling-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' could not be disabled.",
  "plugin-enabling-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' could not be enabled.",
  "plugin-runtime-problem": "الاضافة '{{plugin-name}} لديه مشكلة أثناء التشغيل.",
  "forge-confirm-problem": "Forge requires your confirmation to apply changes and start the server.",
  "mod-dependency-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' is missing the required mod {{dependency-mod-name}}.",
  "mod-dependency-problem-plural": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' is missing the required mods {{dependency-mod-list}}.",
  "mod-duplicate-problem": "تم العثور على اكثر من ملف للمود '{{mod-name}}' في أماكن {{first-mod-path}} و {{second-mod-path}}",
  "mod-exception-problem": "لقد طرح التعديل {{mod-name}} استثناء.",
  "mod-fatal-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' has a fatal error.",
  "world-missing-mod-problem": "The world was saved with mod '{{mod-name}}' which appears to be missing.",
  "world-mod-version-problem": "This world was saved with mod '{{mod-name}}' version {{mod-expected-version}} and it is now at version {{mod-current-version}}.",
  "plugin-incompatible-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' is incompatible with your current server version.",
  "aquatic-world-on-older-version-problem": "The current world was created/loaded with Minecraft 1.13 or higher. The new format cannot be loaded in any older version.",
  "old-player-directory-problem": "The server has detected an old player directory in the world save.",
  "command-run-solution": "Run the command '{{command}}'.",
  "authme-shutdown-solution": "اضبط \"ايقاف الخادم\" الى 'صواب'.",
  "configure-plugin": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}}.",
  "configure-plugin-with-file": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}} ({{suggested-file}}).",
  "plugin-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different version of the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-install-solution": "تحميل الاضافة '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-remove-solution": "حذف الاضافة '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "file-delete-solution": "حذف الملف '{{file-path}}'.",
  "file-edit-solution": "عدل الملف '{{file-path}}'.",
  "mod-install-different-version-solution": "حمل اصدار أخر من التعديل '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-install-solution": "ثبت التعديل '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-install-solution-with-version": "ثبت التعديل '{{mod-name}}' بأِصدار {{mod-version}}.",
  "mod-remove-solution": "أزل التعديل '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "aquatic-version-install-solution": "حدث برنامج الخادم ل1.13 او أحدث.",
  "plugin-command-exception-problem": "الاضافة '{{plugin-name}}' لم تقدر علي تنفيذ الأمر '{{command}}'.",
  "ticking-block-entity-problem": "حجر في العالم يسبب مشاكل.",
  "remove-block-solution": "أزل الحجر من العالم، على سبيل المثال ببرنامج MCEdit.",
  "do-nothing-solution": "لا تفعل شيئا. هذه المشكلة سوف تصلح نفسها.",
  "chunk-load-exception-problem": "حدث خطأ أثناء تحميل قطع العالم.\n",
  "remove-chunk-solution": "أزل القطعة المسببة للمشاكل من العالم,على سبيل المثال ببرنامج MCEdit أو بأِزالة الملف region.",
  "multiverse-load-problem": "العالم '{{world-name}}' لم يتم تحميله لأنه يحتوي علي أخطاء وهو فاسد على الأرجح.",
  "world-repair-solution": "أصلح العالم '{{world-name}}',على سبيل المثال ببرنامج Minecraft Region Fixer أو MCEdit.",
  "world-duplicate-problem": "العالم '{{world-name}}' هو نسخة مكررة من عالم أخر وتم منعه من التحميل.",
  "mod-wrong-minecraft-version-problem": "التعديل '{{mod-name}}' ليس متوافقًا مع اصدار اللعبة {{minecraft-version}}.",
  "forge-install-different-version-solution": "قم بتحميل اصدار اخر من فورج.",
  "malformed-encoding-problem": "شئ (غالبًا الMOTD) يحتوي على رموز تنسيق مشوهة.",
  "change-motd-solution": "غير MOTD الخادم.",
  "bedrock-authentication-whitelist-problem": "Using a whitelist without online authentication is not allowed.",
  "disable-whitelist-solution": "Disable the whitelist.",
  "enable-authentication-solution": "فعل المصادقة عبر الإنترنت.",
  "undefined-mod-dependency-problem": "A mod is missing the required mod {{dependency-mod-name}}.",
  "version-downgrade-problem": "تم استخدام عالمك على إصدار أحدث من قبل.",
  "version-downgrade-solution": "تثبيت نسخة أحدث من ماين كرافت.",
  "generate-new-world-solution": "إنشاء عالم جديد."
}